Seb Lee

EXPERIENCE

Immersive Labs, Bristol

Mid Frontend Developer JANUARY 2023 - FEBRUARY 2024

Associate Frontend Developer JULY 2022 - JANUARY 2023

Junior Software Engineer SEPTEMBER 2021 - JULY 2022

As a developer at Immersive Labs, I helped transform the product from a cybersecurity training platform aimed at individuals and SMEs to enterprise software that could remain stable and accessible for millions of users. I was promoted twice during my time at Immersive Labs for my impact in the engineering team.

- Delivered features and functionality in Typescript, React and GraphQL for a Ruby on Rails backend.
- Worked closely with Data, UX and Customer Success teams to design and build customer-focused features.
- Wrote and maintained end to end tests in Testcafe and Playwright.
- Participated in and led initiatives to improve frontend performance and monitoring.
- Member of the DX Guild, maintaining and building internal tooling.
- Aided in rebuilding the internal component library with developer experience and accessibility in mind.
- Mentored and held regular pairing sessions with a junior developer

01 Group, Remote

Frontend Developer APRIL 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2021

Contract work I took on via personal recommendation of one of my bootcamp coaches.

- Built features for project management software from the ground up in Angular
- Helped to inform design and backend API structure as features were being built out

_nology, Remote

Trainee Software Developer JANUARY 2021 - APRIL 2021

My software development bootcamp involved professional work, building a minimum viable product for a startup.

- Developed a React web app for a food ordering system.
- Served as project manager on the third sprint.
- Built the end-to-end tests and continuous integration pipelines for the project.

107 Weston Road Long Ashton BS41 9AE 07909964550 sebastian.ma.lee@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I am a software engineer from Bristol with three years of professional experience. I specialise in frontend development in the Javascript ecosystem. After two great years at Immersive Labs I'm excited to re-enter the job market and work on interesting new projects.

LANGUAGES

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript / Typescript
- Python

LIBRARIES

- React
- SCSS
- Styled Components
- Tailwind
- Node
- Apollo

FRAMEWORKS

- Next
- Angular

EDUCATION

dBS Music & Sound Institute 2017-2019 MA Sound for Games & Apps (*Pass with Distinction*) 2015-2017 BA Sound for Games & Apps (*First Class Honours*)